In this lesson, we'll create the HGTV server monitor task, as I mentioned previously, this task simply
receives messages from the cube and updates global variables within the monitor task, which affects
certain actions of the web server and the web page.
And there are probably multiple ways to do this.
I just thought it might be useful to update the global variables in one place and also use this as an
opportunity to demonstrate just one way of accomplishing in a task communication between the Wi-Fi application
and the web server.
All right, so now let's start by creating the HTP server.
Monitor, task handle.
And that will be a static test candle type.
And call it task HTP server monitor.
And set that to no.
Next, we'll create the Q handle.
Used to manipulate the main cue of events.
And it's a static to handle type.
And call it HGTV Server Monitor, Q Handle.
And now let's come down to our to DOS.
We have our to dos right here.
And let's create the HTTP server monitor desk.
And also create the message queue.
OK, so here we can use X to create Penta Core.
And we'll call the function HTP server monitor.
And the tag can be the same.
And the stack size will be FTP server monitor.
Stack size.
And PV parameters will be No.
And the priority will be HTTP server monitor priority.
And our test scandal is a reference to the task HTP server monitor.
And now the Korede is HTTP server monitor, core aid.
OK, it looks good.
So later, we'll define the HTTP server monitored task you.
OK, now let's create the cue message and it'll be H-2B server monitor, queue handle.
Equals excu creates.
And it's 3:00 here and the size of.
HTTP server tube message types.
All right, so next, let's define the HTP server monetary task.
So we'll head up you.
And let's make a comment.
That says HTTP server monitor task.
Used to track events of the FTP server.
And the parameter is point of variable parameter, p parameter.
Which can be passed to the task.
And this is a static void.
HTP server monitor, and that's a void point of parameter.
And here, first, we need an instance of the Q message scandal.
So HGTV server monitor Q message type.
And call it message.
And next will create an endless loop.
And then say, if excu receive.
And let's include our handle here.
And the reference to the message then put Max delay.
OK.
Then say switch.
Message, short message, I'd.
And then let's open a case.
And we want to use our messages here, so let's come here and grab the first one.
And then let's drop it right here.
And then let's lug a message for this message.
And then we can break.
All right, so let me just fix this indentation.
And then copy that.
So we can paste it down.
Then let's grab the next message.
And then update this case.
And we'll just do the same procedure for the next.
Copy the message.
And update the case.
And let's keep it going.
For this message.
OK, and on to the next.
Get the message.
Update the case.
And one more time.
Grab the message.
And update this case.
OK, so now let's just leave a default break here.
OK, great.
So we'll want to be able to stop the FTP server monitor if the HTP server is stopped as well, so let's
grab the handle.
And then let's come down to the HTP server stop function.
And then we'll see if task HGTV server monitor.
Then we will ask delete.
And insert that same handle here.
OK, now log message.
That says HGTV servers stop.
Stopping FTP server monitor.
All right, now, let's set the handle to know.
OK, it looks good.
So that completes our stop function.
Now let's head over to the head of file.
So we can copy the send message prototype.
And we could define it right here.
So first, create an instance of the HGTV server Q message type.
Do we want the message I'd set to the message I'd passed to the function?
And then we'll return the result of excuse sent.
In pass the handle.
And the reference to the message and Port Max delay.
OK.
All looks good, so now we can build.
And we have no errors, so we're ready for firmware updates.
So we'll talk about that in the next section, and I'll see you then.